Contact

awyldeberry@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/amy-berry-rn-ccrn-432937123 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Advanced Cardiac Life Support Mental Health Med/Surg

Certifications CCRN

Honors-Awards

Beacon Award of Excellence

Amy Berry RN, CCRN

Critical Care RN at St. Elizabeth Healthcare Burlington, Kentucky

Summary

Energetic, dedicated bedside RN, 13years, actively involved in unit based and hospital wide initiatives to improve patient outcomes. Chair Peer Mentor Committee, Co-Chair Preceptor Coordinator Council, Compassion fatigue initiative, Bereavement Committee, CAUTI reduction unit champion, Unit Based Council member, Critical Care Skills day Facilitator, CRRT & Hypothermia trainer, PD super user. I have held the position as MICU Preceptor Coordinator for 4+ years, onboarding and mentoring new hires. CN III

Experience

St. Elizabeth Healthcare
Critical Care RN
September 2012 - Present (7 years 11 months)
Edgewood, KY

24 bed Medical Intensive Care Unit
10 bed Surgical Intensive Care Unit
CCRT, Sepsis, ARDS, Hypothermia, CVA, SDH, SAH, post op surgical
patients, s/p Craniotomy

NorthKey Community Care RN January 2015 - October 2015 (10 months) Covington,KY

Mental Health community clinic & Homeless outreach. RN to APRN, managing patients ranging from anxiety, depression to Bipolar, schizophrenia. Welcome House liasion for Homeless Service Project grant

Dearborn County Hospital Med/Surg RN January 2007 - September 2012 (5 years 9 months) Lawrenceburg, IN Charge Nurse of an 18 bed Med/Surg unit, patient population consisting of: Pulmonary- including chronic ventilator management, acute opiate withdrawal, ESRD and end of life/comfort care.

Education

Good Samaritan College of Nursing & Health Science Associate's Degree, Nursing · (2004 - 2006)